## Matthew J Angle

727 Cumberland Ave Chambersburg, PA 17201 (717) 372-6021 mjangle1985@gmail.com

#### Overview

I'm a committed and hardworking professional with experience leading teams, making plans and meeting goals. I'm currently enrolled as full-time student at Shippensburg University, where I'm working on my senior research which involves augmenting medical image datasets with GAN based synthetic images to improve CNN accuracy.

I previously worked for the University Engineering Department as support for our system administrator. I love working with Linux and Python and most of my personal projects currently revolve around Linux or Python. I enjoy most things related to data, including scraping/sourcing, transforming, and interpreting data.

#### TECHNOLOGY

#### Programming Languages:

SKILLS

R, Python, C, C++, Java, HTML/CSS, SQL

Tools and Technologies:

Tidyverse, Pandas/NumPy, JUnit, Linux (multiple distros), VMware, Git, LAMP

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Software Engineering Shippensburg University of Pennsylvania, Shippensburg, PA 2018 - Present

- Data Science Club
- Linux Administration Club

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Philosophy Temple University, Philadelphia, PA 2007 - 2009

• Temple University Undergraduate Philosophy Society, Secretary.

# ${\bf PROFESSIONAL}\ Engineering\ Support\ Student$

2020

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Shippensburg University, Shippensburg, PA

- Student support for department system administrator
- $\bullet$  Working with administration utilities, VM ware, ClusterSSH, Active Directory, Linux-PAM

Financial Advisor

2016 - 2017

Edward Jones, Chambersburg, PA

- Assisted my clients in planning future financial goals like paying for their child's education, retirement, and estate concerns.
- Series 7, and 66.

Teller Supervisor

2015 - 2016

Orrstown Bank, Chambersubrg, PA

• Coached teller team to meet sales goals.